Good morning
ießen
c
Oh!
Hello.
I'm Kobi Suzuki from Hinatazaka 46.
Let me tell you where the stars are right now.
Ta-da!
Can you see it?
We are here in Dexas.
This is Union Tower in Dallas.
I'm just climbing up to the top.
This time, I'm here for a photo shoot on September 6th.
I'm here for a photo shoot for a collaboration project between Bots Press and New Era, and
And I'm here in Texas to see the All-Star Game.
I came to Texas to see the All-Star Game.
MLB All-Star game
Continuing from last year
I'll be there!
I'm really looking forward to it.
I didn't think I would be able to go two years in a row,
This year's event will be even more exciting than last year's,
I'm hoping to share some of it with those of you who watch Hinatazaka-channer.
So please enjoy yourselves.
It's the start of the "Sutexas Night" trip.
Steckisus!
Can you see this place?
Dallas World Aquarium
I am now at the Shinjuku Pavilion.
Today I am...
I have an explorer's look, so I invite you all to join me on this adventure.
Look, look. Look at the penguins.
So cute.
I'm a little addicted to seeing convergence in all sorts of places, so
I've got all the staff involved.
I brought them to the convergence.
It's really amazing.
It's like a real jungle.
I got a lot of looks from the little kids.
They were like, "What's this? They were like...
What is this? Like, "Jonxie.
What's this? Like, "What's this?
Oh, Danger Zone, Dangerous Zone.
Is Dangerous G here?
Algaejol?
He's not here.
Where is this?
I heard there's an alligator.
Crocodile, crocodile, crocodile, crocodile.
Crocodiles.
Where is it?
Oh!
There it is.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello, sir.
unreal to the cross.
olly
w
I'm laughing.
The ...
A being eaten
Let's get you in there.
This position is in.
Ta-da!
In and out.
We're at the famous hamburger place.
Oh, America!
I'm feeling America.
Star!
Amazing!
Cheeseburger!
This is Animal Style!
I'll eat alone!
Bon appétit!
Oh!
Mechachu!
And the fries are delicious too!
Port Worth Stockyards
Here we are at the Texas Camansai place!
They sell a lot of pengalong hearts and whiskey dice!
I'm off to have pancakes here!
I'm going to eat pancakes here.
It's all about the Wallstar.
So many different teams.
Now Cat, this is a lot of Rangers' Cat, too.
Me too.
Good morning.
We're here inside Globe Life Field, home of the Texas Rangers.
We're now participating in the practices that we were allowed to do last year.
Congratulations.
Now let's go to the Grapes.
I'm going to try to have a sea
Start.
Start
Start. - Start.
Men!
Yes!
Now that morning practice is over, we're going to eat!
This is the picture we just got.
They put it in this frame and gave it to me as a gift!
I'm so bent over, it's embarrassing!
It's a souvenir.
This is what breakfast looks like.
Breakfast after morning practice
Here are today's souvenirs!
Ta-da!
I made a picture of Otani
I chose a picture of the FATIONAL LEAGUE with Otani.
It's so cute!
The league is pink here and beige here.
and this one is blue and black.
I got this as a commemorative gift.
Yay!
Here you go.
How do you like it?
It's great.
There's a bond between the audience and the fans, just like on the field.
In the rock 'n' roll, with the people around you. It's great.
I knew what he was talking about when I met him two years ago.
It's really great.
Thank you.
Mr. and Mrs. Lunch makeup
Sharon read
A stopover on last month's trip
acerca
Interlude
A chance to hear Mom's voice
Now and before
I don't know when in my life I'll get the chance.
so I'm
I'm so happy to see him.
He is a wonderful person, a friend, and seeing him every day is a big thanks to him.
What kind of player are you now?
What kind of player are you?
What kind of player is he now?
He was a wonderful person. It was a dream come true.
I was able to hear what I wanted to see, and I feel like I want to go to Japan,
I will be waiting for you in Japan.
I'll be waiting for you in Japan. A GRASS player did it. I'm very happy.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your time.
Good morning.
Good morning
I will go into the blog life
Looking forward to
This Regenzi has come up
Regenzi has come up
Good luck!
Ohtani hit a home run!
Amazing!
Three runs!
Unbelievable!
He's a star after all!
Arrangers
Glad to hear from you, Sullivan's.
Thanks for taking a look.